littletikes.com 2013-08-06

# privacypolicy

**_LITTLE TIKES PRIVACY POLICY_**

The Little Tikes Company (Little Tikes) is a an MGA Entertainment Inc. company and this Privacy Policy applies to the Little Tikes web site, and all related websites (each a “Site”) owned by MGA Entertainment, Inc. and its affiliated and subsidiary companies (”MGA”). Little Tikes wants to give you the most exciting Internet experience possible. Because your privacy is important to us, Little Tikes provides this notice explaining what kinds of information we collect online and how we use it, as well as the choices you can make regarding the information collected.

You can participate in many features on the Site without providing any personally identifiable information. By (1) using this Site, (2) supplying any personal information via the Site, and/or (3) supplying any personal information to Little Tikes in response to any email or other form of communication from Little Tikes that references this Privacy Policy, you acknowledge your agreement with this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THE TERMS STATED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SITE.

If you place orders by mail, phone or on this Site, we do make out mailing list available to carefully screened companies whose products or services might interest you.  If you prefer to have your name withheld, simply let us know by sending an email to: [littletikes.cares@littletikescare.com](mailto:littletikes.cares@littletikescare.com).

Sections of this Site may be subject to additional privacy terms and you will be notified of this when using the applicable sections of the Site.  You should carefully review these additional privacy terms before using those sections; such additional privacy terms will not replace or change this Privacy Policy, except when expressly stated otherwise.  
We collect information, including personal information, for a variety of business reasons, including, for example:  (i) establishing and maintaining relations and/or contact with customers and potential customers; (ii) understanding your needs and preferences; (iii) developing, enhancing, marketing, promoting and/or providing goods and/or services to meet your needs or expectations, (iv) allowing you to participate in contests, sweepstakes and other promotions; (v) fulfilling legal and/or regulatory requirements; and (vi) for such additional purposes as may be identified to you from time to time (each, a “Purpose”).  By way of example only, the Site may enable you to order products; enter contests, sweepstakes or other promotions; vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion; subscribe to one of our services such as online newsletters; or participate in an online forum or community

**TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT**

The types of personal information that may be collected from you include: your name, shipping or street address, billing address, e-mail addresses, passwords, date of birth, product selections, telephone number, fax number, credit card or other payment information, demographic information (such as your age, age range, gender, and/or purchase history information), and information about your interests in, and use or purchase of, various products, programs and services.  At certain parts of the Site, only persons who provide us with the requested personal information will be able to participate in the activities and offerings at that part of the Site. 

All personal information that is collected is done so with the voluntary permission of the visitor over 13 years of age, or with the verifiable consent of a parent or guardian of anyone 13 years or younger.  Little Tikes will not keep personally identifiable information collected from a child 13 years or younger, except with verifiable parent or guardian consent or if the information is in aggregated form (e.g., 50% of the respondents were girls under the age of 13). 

You may also be able to submit personal information at the Site about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, street address, e-mail address, and telephone number.  Little Tikes will not use such personal information about other people unless that other person has consented to such use. 

We also collect certain anonymous or non-personally identifiable information when you visit some of our Site pages, such as the Site pages that you visited, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape or Internet Explorer), the level of encryption that your web browser supports, the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), the name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink), the query that you entered into a search engine via a Site or which led you to the Site, and any other “click stream” data. We use this anonymous or non-personally identifiable information for the Purposes outlined above, as well as for technical, research and analytical purposes, including for instance, to rate and improve the design and content of the Site and to enable us to personalize your experience.  We may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze how the Site is used and to offer you products, services, promotions, sweepstakes and contests.

**E-mail**  
By allowing you to send e-mail to us, we are not attempting to collect any personal information about you. Except as otherwise explained in this Privacy Policy, we will only use any personal information (such as name and e-mail address) contained in your e-mail to us to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the e-mail. 

**Promotions**  
To participate in some of our promotions, you may be asked to provide an e-mail address or screen name, so that we can let you know if you won a prize. For other Little Tikes promotions, we may request your name and home address in order to send you products or information by regular mail. We will only gather this information after we have received verifiable parental consent to do so. 

**Resumes  
**The Little Tikes site and other MGA Sites allow for the online submission of resumes in conjunction with job applications. Personal information collected by us in allowing for resume submission will be used solely for the purpose of accepting and evaluating candidate submissions for job postings as further explained in the relevant portion of applicable Sites. This information may be shared within the company and with third parties assisting Little Tikes with its recruitment efforts, in both cases, in confidence and when there is a legitimate business purpose and reason for accessing it.  

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Cookies allow websites to “remember” a user's activities on a website as well as a user's visits to a site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer by a web page server.  At the Little Tikes site and at other MGA Sites, cookies are used to determine the number of unique visitors over a given period. In addition, we sometimes use cookies to show us how people found the Site, which pages they visited and how long they stayed. We may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our Sites.  You can of course, disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser.

We may also use "web beacons" through a third party content server that monitors your use of our Sites. Web beacons (or web bugs) are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page for the purpose of transferring data, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the web beacon appears, the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the page on which the web beacon appears, the time the page containing the web beacon was viewed, the types of browsers that fetched the web beacon and the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server. When corresponding with you via HTML capable e-mail, web beacons let us know whether you received and opened our e-mail.

On their own, cookies or web beacons do not contain or reveal any personally identifiable information. However, if you choose to furnish the Site with personally identifiable information, this information can be linked to the data stored in the cookies/web beacons.

By accepting this Privacy Policy, you specifically agree to our use of cookies and web beacons as described herein. You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other web site. Additionally, by setting your web browser to display HTML e-mails as text only, you may be able to prevent the use of some web beacons. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. However, certain areas of our Sites can only be accessed in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our Site content. 

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION**

Personal information that you provide to Little Tikes will only be used with your consent for the Purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.  We use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other or new products, programs or services or to offer you information about other or new products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

We also use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests, sweepstakes or other promotions, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your registration and/or account with us.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts, cards or greetings. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs or services to them or to offer them information about other or new products, programs or services. The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs or services or to offer you information about other or new products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you choose to submit content for publication, such as a photograph sent as part of a promotion or sweepstake, and we may publish your screen name or your first name and last initial and other information you have provided to us, such as the city or state where you are located. We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs or services or to offer you information about other or new products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

Little Tikes will only disclose personally identifiable information to third parties with your consent or in the limited instances set forth in this Privacy Policy.  Your personally identifiable information may sometimes be shared with other Little Tikes and other MGA affiliates and subsidiaries, who will be bound by the same terms set out in this Privacy Policy.  In addition, in the course of daily operations, authorized Little Tikes employees may be provided with access to personally identifiable information.  Any use of such personally identifiable information by Little Tikes employees will be in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  Your personally identifiable information may be disclosed in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, imminent danger to life or property that might be avoided or minimized by disclosure of such information, or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as may be otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you to an acquiring or merging party, if Little Tikes or a portion of its business is acquired by or merged with another company.

From time to time, Little Tikes may provide personally identifiable information to agents and contractors of Little Tikes who are performing services for Little Tikes.  Such third parties are required to protect this personally identifiable information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Little Tikes.

If we intend to share personally identifiable information about you to companies that may want to market products or services to you (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases), we will ask for your permission at the relevant Site where we request such information. If at some point you grant us permission to transfer your information for these purposes and later decide that you no longer want us to do so, simply send us an email at littletikes.cares@littletikescare.com and we'll change your preferences accordingly.

We may occasionally combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you register with our Site, we provide you with an opportunity to express your preferences with respect to receiving details about other products and services from Little Tikes, MGA, affiliated businesses and selected third parties, as well as information about other or new products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, whether from Little Tikes, MGA or from affiliated businesses and selected third parties (such as licensees). If you ever decide in the future that you would like to update these preferences, you may do so by sending us an email at [littletikes.cares@littletikescare.com](mailto:littletikes.cares@littletikescare.com) and we'll change your preferences accordingly.

We will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt-out, as described more fully below. 

**SAFEGUARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Little Tikes will only collect personal information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will take appropriate steps to safeguard the security and integrity of any information you provide to us. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial security procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect online.  We periodically review these security practices and adopt new technologies and procedures in order to protect your personal information.  Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot, however, absolutely ensure that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. 

**OPT-OUT, UPDATES AND REMOVAL OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If you have provided us with any personal information and do not want Little Tikes to retain this information or wish to update or correct it, you can notify us at any time by calling 1-800-321-0183 or sending us an e-mail at littletikes.cares@littletikescare.com and we will remove this information from our database or correct it as directed by you. You may also update your information yourself in certain portions of the Site, through use of the user name and password that you have chosen.  Little Tikes will respond to customer requests for the release of personal information about such customer’s account only to the email address on file with Little Tikes.  It is your responsibility to maintain the security and integrity of that email address.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Visitors to this Site may participate in many activities without providing any personally identifiable information. However, if a visitor wants to participate in certain of our interactive features, we may ask the visitor to register and provide us with their e-mail address and age information. When the person who registers indicates that he or she is 13 years or younger, we will either collect no personally identifiable information from that individual or, if we are collecting personally identifiable information, we will inform the child that verifiable consent from a parent or legal guardian is required. We may collect the e-mail address of the user's parent or legal guardian in addition to the user's e-mail address, and use the e-mail address of the parent or legal guardian to seek that person's verifiable consent and ask the parent or legal guardian to provide certain personal information including home address. In the alternative, Little Tikes may notify the parent or legal guardian of his/her child's online activities and enable that person to unsubscribe his/her child from a newsletter or other similar activity. If a user is 13 years or younger, we will not condition his/her participation in an online activity on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. We do not share children's information with outside third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy.

Parents or legal guardians may at any time review, update or delete from our database any personally identifiable information that we have collected online from their child and/or request that there be no further collection or use of their child's information by calling us at 1-800-321-0183 or sending an e-mail to littletikes.cares@littletikescare.com, or sending a letter to: 

**Little Tikes Consumer Service**

**2180 Barlow Road** ****

**Hudson** **, Ohio 44236 USA** ****

Please be sure to include in your message the e-mail address you used to register so that we can verify your request. 

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD PARTY SITES AND SPONSORS**

Some of our Sites contain links to other web sites whose information practices may be different than ours and that are not governed by this Privacy Policy. Visitors should consult the other web sites' privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, collected by, used and/or disclosed by these third parties. Little Tikes is not responsible for the privacy policies employed by any other websites.  In addition, we may sometimes offer activities (e.g., contests, sweepstakes or promotions) that are sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the Site activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of this information. If third parties will have access to personally identifiable information that you are being asked to provide, this Site will notify you at the time such personally identifiable information is requested. 

**NOTIFICATION REGARDING UPDATES  
  
**

This Privacy Policy is being posted and effective on March 17, 2007. Little Tikes reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting any such changes here on the Site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it, and how this Privacy Policy may have changed since the time when you first reviewed it.

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us a **t:**[ privacy@mgae.com](mailto:privacy@mgae.com?subject=Privacy%20Information) or at MGA Entertainment, Inc.,  Attn. Chief Privacy Officer, 16380 Roscoe Boulevard, Van Nuys, CA 91406. **____**

**Disclaimer Regarding Electronic Messages and Postings**

Being a part of LittleTikes.com Means Acting Responsibly!

By using this Site, you agree to the following:

When sending E-mail, E-Greetings or making a submission or a posting, DO NOT:

1.      Upload, post, transmit or make available in any way, any material that may be deemed as unlawful, harmful, abusive, defamatory, hateful, racially hurtful, targeting a particular racial or religious group, inappropriate for children or otherwise questionable;

2.      Harm minors or suggest harm to minors in any way;

3.      Impersonate any person or entity, or falsely state or misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity, or falsely state or misrepresent you age;

4.      Upload, post, transmit or make available in any way any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional, solicitation materials or inappropriate or otherwise questionable materials of any kind’

5.      Upload, post, transmit or make available any material that contains software viruses or tampers, destroys or limits the ability to function of a computer, website, personal e-mail account or corporate computer network or website.

Thank You.
